A Guide to the Minutes of the Virginia Code Commission, 1970-2005
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Minutes of the Virginia Code Commission, 1970-2005
The Library of Virginia
51824
9 cu. ft. (9 boxes)
Virginia Code Commission
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred on 14 June 2016 by the Division of Legislative Services, General Assembly Bldg, 201 North 9th St., Richmond, VA 23219.
Biographical Information
The Commission on Code Recodification was created by an act of the General Assembly passed on March 30, 1946. Its principal duty was to make a complete recodification of the statute laws of the state of a general nature. This task was completed two years later, and the new code was approved by the General Assembly on March 30, 1948.
An act passed by the General Assembly on March 16, 1948, made the commission a permanent agency of the legislative branch of government and changed the name of the commission to the Virginia Code Commission. The commission supervises the codification of the statutes after each General Assembly session and revises and recodifies portions of the Code of Virginia as needed.
In 1992 the Commission was charged with the responsibility of creating Virginia's first administrative code of regulations by compiling and codifying all of the administrative regulations of state agencies. The Commission also oversees the bi-weekly publication of The Virginia Register of Regulations, which is used by state agencies during the adoption of new regulations to be included in the Administrative Process Act.
Scope and Content
Minutes and related attachments, 1970-2005, documenting the meetings, activities, discussions, policy decisions, and recommendations of the Virginia Code Commission. In addition to minutes, also includes correspondence, memoranda, reports, resolutions, and copies of regulations, legislation and statutes.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically, except for 2005 which is out of order.
Contents List
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1970-1979 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 1)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 January 10-31 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 2)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1979 December 14-1980 January 8 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 3)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 March 14-31 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 4)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 April 21 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 5)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 May 5-22 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 6)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 June 20-26 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 7)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 July 24 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 8)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 August 28 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 9)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 September 10 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 10)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 September 26 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 11)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 October 30-November 7 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 12)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 November 11-29 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 13)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 December 17 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 14)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1980 December 19-1981 January 10 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 15)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1981 March 10-31 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 16)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1981 April 28 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 17)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1981 June 5 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 18)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1981 July 16-17 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 19)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1981 August 21-25 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 20)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1981 September 22 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 21)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1981 November 11 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 22)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1981 December 1-2 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 23)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1982 July 27 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 24)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1982 October 26-December 3 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 25)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1982 December 13 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 26)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1983 April 7 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 27)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1983 June 17-18 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 28)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1983 August 15-16 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 29)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1983 October 12 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 30)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1983 October 24 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 31)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1983 November 29-30 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 32)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1983 December 23-27 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 33)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1984 April 16-May 21 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 34)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1984 July 30-September 4 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 35)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1984 August 30-31 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 36)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1984 October 1 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 37)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1984 July 30-October 24 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 38)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1984 November 1-December 5 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 39)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1985 May 13-23 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 40)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1985 June 25-27 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 41)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1985 August 28 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 42)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1985 October 10 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 43)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1985 September 6-December 2 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 44)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1986 March 17-April 11 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 45)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1986 May 7-June 25 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 46)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1985 August 18-27 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 47)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1986 January 9-October 31 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 48)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1986 December 2-30 (Box 1 [box 128], Folder 49)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1987 June 16-17 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 1)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1987 September 1-2 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 2)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1987 November 30 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 3)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1987 December 18 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 4)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1988 April 187 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 5)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1988 June 17 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 6)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1988 September 2 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 7)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1988 October 6-7 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 8)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1988 November 28 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 9)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1988 December 15 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 10)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1989 May 11-12 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 11)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1989 September 5 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 12)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1989 November 3 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 13)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1989 December 19 (Box 2 [box 129], Folder 14)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1990 January 18 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 1)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1990 April 24 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 2)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1990 June 12 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 3)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1990 October 11-12 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 4)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1990 November 20 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 5)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1990 December 14 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 6)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1991 March 19 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 7)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1991 September 4-5 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 8)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1991 November 27 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 9)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1991 December 11 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 10)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1992 February 12 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 11)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1992 April 14 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 12)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1992 June 3 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 13)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1992 June 24 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 14)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1992 July 15 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 15)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1992 August 19 (Box 3 [box 130], Folder 16)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1992 September 16 (Box 4 [box 131], Folder 1)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1992 October 22 (Box 4 [box 131], Folder 2)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1992 November 18 (Box 4 [box 131], Folder 3)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1992 December 17 (Box 4 [box 131], Folder 4)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1993 April 29 (Box 4 [box 131], Folder 5)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1993 June 16 (Box 4 [box 131], Folder 6)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1993 July 20 (Box 4 [box 131], Folder 7)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1993 August 17-19 (Box 4 [box 131], Folder 8)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1993 September 15 (Box 4 [box 131], Folder 9)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1993 October 20 (Box 4 [box 131], Folder 10)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1993 November 17 (Box 4 [box 131], Folder 11)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1994 April 19 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 1)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1994 May 13 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 2)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1994 June 15 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 3)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1994 July 7 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 4)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1994 August 17 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 5)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1994 September 26 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 6)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1994 October 19 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 7)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1994 November 16 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 8)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1994 December 21 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 9)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1995 March 15 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 10)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1995 May 17 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 11)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1995 August 16-17 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 12)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1995 September 20 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 13)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1995 November 15-16 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 14)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1995 December 20 (Box 5 [box 132], Folder 15)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1996 March 28 (Box 6 [box 133], Folder 1)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1996 April 25 (Box 6 [box 133], Folder 2)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1996 May 16 (Box 6 [box 133], Folder 3)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1996 June 19-20 (Box 6 [box 133], Folder 4)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1996 July 10-11 (Box 6 [box 133], Folder 5)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1996 September 18 (Box 6 [box 133], Folder 6)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1996 November 19 (Box 6 [box 133], Folder 7)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1997 March 26 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 1)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1997 May 16 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 2)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1997 August 13 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 3)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1997 October 29 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 4)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1998 January 7 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 5)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1998 April 29 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 6)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1998 June 10 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 7)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1998 July 8 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 8)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1998 November 18 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 9)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1999 June 21 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 10)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1999 August 18 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 11)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1999 September 13 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 12)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1999 October 18 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 13)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1999 November 9 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 14)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 1999 December 15-16 (Box 7 [box 134], Folder 15)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2000 June 20 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 1)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2000 July 24 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 2)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2000 August 16 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 3)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2000 September 27-28 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 4)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2000 November 27 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 5)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2001 January 5 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 6)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2001 March 26 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 7)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2001 April 6 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 8)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2001 May 16 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 9)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2001 June 28 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 10)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2001 July 26 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 11)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2001 August 30 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 12)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2001 October 3-4 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 13)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2001 November 15 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 14)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2001 December 13 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 15)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2005 April 20 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 16)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2005 May 23 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 17)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2005 June 15 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 18)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2005 July 27 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 19-20)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2005 August 17 (Box 8 [box 135], Folder 21)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2002 April 16 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 1)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2002 July 17 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 2)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2002 August 21 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 3)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2002 October 2 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 4)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2002 November 7 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 5)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2002 December 3 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 6)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2003 April 2 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 7)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2003 May 21 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 8)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2003 August 20 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 9)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2003 September 17 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 10)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2003 October 22 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 11)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2003 November 19 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 12)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2003 December 9 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 13)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2004 March 10 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 14)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2004 May 19 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 15)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2004 July 14-15 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 16)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2004 August 18 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 17)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2004 September 15 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 18)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2004 October 20 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 19)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2004 November 17 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 20)
- Meeting minutes and supporting documents, 2004 December 15 (Box 9 [box 136], Folder 21)